https://www.watersedgegolf.com/article/terms-of-use

Terms of Use
Welcome to Water's Edge Golf Club's Website. This site is managed by Billy Casper Golf, LLC, whose registered office is 12700 Sunrise Valley Dr, Suite 300, Reston, Virginia 20191. References to the terms “we” and “us” in these Terms of Use refer to Billy Casper Golf, its subsidiaries, and affiliates, and each of their officers, shareholders and employees.BY ACCESSING, USING, OR DOWNLOADING MATERIALS FROM THIS SITE, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THESE TERMS OF USE (“TERMS”), JUST AS IF YOU HAD SIGNED THESE TERMS IN A PAPER CONTRACT. IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THESE TERMS, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS SITE.The information on this Site is provided without charge as a convenience to visitors, to be used only for informational purposes. While we have tried to provide accurate and timely information, there may be inadvertent technical or factual inaccuracies and typographical errors, for which we apologize. We reserve the right to make changes and corrections at any time, without notice.Legal Disclaimer. THE MATERIALS AND SERVICES PROVIDED AT THIS SITE ARE PROVIDED “AS IS,” “AS AVAILABLE,” AND WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, WE DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY. Further, we do not warrant that the functions contained in the materials on this site will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that this site or the servers that make such materials available are free of viruses or other harmful components. We do not warrant or make any representations regarding the use or the results of the use of the materials on this site in terms of their correctness, accuracy, reliability, or otherwise. You assume the entire cost of all necessary servicing, repair, or correction. We may make changes to the materials and services at this site, including the temporary or permanent cessation of all or any portion of this site, at any time without notice. Applicable law may not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, so the above exclusions may not apply to you.Liability. You assume all responsibility and risk for the use of this site. Decisions based on information contained in this site are your sole responsibility, and in exchange for using this site you agree to hold us harmless against any claims for damages arising from any decision you make based on such information. in no event shall we be liable for any damages whatsoever, whether direct, indirect, special, consequential, exemplary, or punitive (including, without limitation, those resulting from lost profits, lost data, or business interruption) arising out of or in any way in connection with the use, inability to use, or the results of use of this site, any web sites linked to this site, or the materials or information or services contained at any or all such sites. These limitations apply whether a claim is based on warranty, contract, tort, strict liability, statute, or any other legal theory, and whether or not you were advised of the possibility of such damages, except for cases of gross (but not ordinary) negligence or willful misconduct on the part of us. If your use of the materials, information, or services from this site results in the need for services, repair, or correction of equipment or data, you assume all costs thereof.Your Sole Remedy. IF YOU ARE DISSATISFIED WITH THIS SITE OR ANY OF THESE TERMS, YOUR SOLE AND EXCLUSIVE REMEDY IS TO DISCONTINUE USING THIS SITE.Applicable Laws, Jurisdiction and Venue. We make no representation that materials or services at this Site are appropriate or available for use outside the United States, and access to them from territories where their contents are illegal is prohibited. You may not use or export or re-export the materials or services at this Site or any copy or adaptations in violation of any applicable laws or regulations, including, without limitation, United States export laws and regulations. If you choose to access this Site from outside the United States, you do so on your own initiative and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws. THESE TERMS WILL BE GOVERNED BY AND CONSTRUED IN ACCORDANCE WITH THE LAWS OF THE COMMONWEALTH OF VIRGINIA, USA, WITHOUT GIVING EFFECT TO ANY choice of law rules which may direct the application of the laws of any other jurisdiction. Any dispute in connection or relating to your use of this Site shall be heard only in a federal or state court of competent jurisdiction located in Fairfax County, Virginia. By using this site, you irrevocably consent to the jurisdiction of such courts. If any of the terms stated herein are found to be unlawful or unenforceable for any reason, that provision will be severable from the rest of these terms and shall not affect the enforceability of the remaining terms. These terms constitute the entire agreement between us with respect to your use of the Site, and these terms may only be amended in a writing signed by an officer of Billy Casper Golf or by Billy Casper Golf posting such amendment on this Site. A printed version of these terms shall be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to these terms or your use of the Site to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form.Hypertext Links. We make no claim or representation regarding, and accept no responsibility for, the quality, content, nature, or reliability of Web sites accessible by hypertext link from this Site, or Web sites linking to this Site. If you decide to access linked third party Web sites, you do so at your own risk and remain responsible for reviewing and abiding by the privacy statements and terms of use posted at any linked Web sites.No Endorsement. References in this Site to any products, services, processes, hypertext links, or other information, by trade name, trade mark, manufacturer, supplier, or otherwise, do not necessarily constitute or imply our endorsement, sponsorship, or recommendation.Rights to Information Submitted. By providing information (such as feedback, data, answers, questions, comments, suggestions, plans, or ideas) to us, you agree that such information shall be non-confidential and non-proprietary. You also agree that we shall have unlimited rights to use (or not to use), to distribute (or not to distribute), to reproduce (or not to reproduce), and to disclose (or not to disclose) such information worldwide as we deem appropriate, without compensation or acknowledgement of its source. This does not apply to personal information, however, and we refer you to our Privacy Policy regarding personal information. We shall be free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques contained in information you provide us through this Site, including but not limited to developing, manufacturing, and marketing products or services incorporating or otherwise based on such information. If you have questions or comments about this Site, use the "Contact Us" link.Framing and Deep Linking Prohibited. You may not frame this Site nor provide a link to a page other than the home page of this Site without our express permission.Copyright Notice. You are responsible for obeying all applicable copyright laws. We permit you to copy materials published on this Site for your personal, non-commercial use or use within the organization that employs you. All names, logos, images, and trademarks may not otherwise by used in any manner without the prior written consent of Billy Casper Golf.Except as otherwise noted, all the contents of this Site and downloads from it are copyrighted by Water's Edge Golf Club. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.Ownership of the Trademarks on this Site. The name Water's Edge Golf Club, its logo, and any other marks used on the Site are trademarks of Billy Casper Golf, its subsidiaries or affiliates.Other names, words, titles, phrases, logos, icons, graphics, or designs contained in this Site may also be considered trademarks, trade names, or design marks of Billy Casper Golf, its subsidiaries or affiliates. The display of such trademarks, trade names, or design marks in this Site (including those specifically mentioned in the preceding paragraph) does not imply that a license of any kind has been granted to any other party. Any unauthorized use regarding publication, copying, or modification of the information contained in this Site, including trademarks, trade names, and design marks, may violate applicable legislation and may result in legal action.General. We may revise these terms at any time by updating this posting. You are advised to visit this page from time to time to review the then-current terms because they are legally binding on you. Certain provisions of these terms may be superseded by expressly designated legal notices located on particular pages at this Site or by terms of any written contracts between you and Billy Casper Golf, its subsidiaries or affiliates.Refund Policy. All gift cards – whether purchased on-line via credit card or in person – are non-refundable, not redeemable for cash, not replaceable if lost or stolen, and expire one year from date of purchase, except where prohibited by law.
Golf
Join
Outings
Events
Dining & Banquets
Improve
Store
BOOK A TEE TIME
Copyright © 2020. Water's Edge Golf Club. 7205 W 115th St, Worth, IL 60482.
Managed by BCG
Privacy PolicyTerms of UseAccessibility Statement
